https://www.24hourdigitizing.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
24HourDigitizing.com takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes exactly how 24HourDigitizing.com uses identifiable information regarding our customers, such as name, address, email address or credit card number ("Customer Information"). Primarily, we collect such information for the purpose of providing you with an outstanding experience on the 24HourDigitizing.com Service. Except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy, 24HourDigitizing.com does not sell, rent or share such Customer Information with third parties.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Customer Service department.
By using our Service, you consent to the collection and use of information in the manner described below. If we decide to change our privacy practice, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Changes to our policy will be prospective only. Please check this page from time to time for changes to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices.
In this Privacy Policy, you will find the answers to the following questions:
* What Customer Information does 24HourDigitizing.com collect?
* How does 24HourDigitizing.com use Customer Information?
* Does 24HourDigitizing.com share Customer Information?
* Does 24HourDigitizing.com use "IP Addresses" and cookies?
* How can you update or correct Customer Information?
* Other information about privacy
What Customer Information does 24HourDigitizing.com collect?
Customer Information is requested whenever you choose to use 24HourDigitizing.com services.  For example:
When you complete a purchase from 24HourDigitizing.com, we will ask you to provide shipping and billing information so that we can fulfill your request.
How does 24HourDigitizing.com use Customer Information?
Our primary goal in collecting your Customer Information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, user-friendly experience on the 24HourDigitizing.com site. Here are the ways we use Customer Information to enhance this experience:
Customer Communication: We use Customer Information to communicate with you and we consider this communication to be an integral part of the 24HourDigitizing.com service. We use your email and mailing address to inform you of site improvements, feature announcements, newsletters, 24HourDigitizing.com promotional offers.
Customer Satisfaction: We use Customer Information to make your 24HourDigitizing.com experience enjoyable. For example, because we know who you are after you log in, we can present you with previous order information in your password-protected virtual account. We also know where to email you to let you know your order is ready for pickup.
Does 24HourDigitizing.com share Customer Information?
24HourDigitizing.com does not share Customer Information with third party intermediaries (for example, credit card authorization companies, photo processing labs, merchandise distributors, vendors processing our outbound email communication, etc).
Other than as described in the previous paragraphs, 24HourDigitizing.com will not sell, rent or otherwise share Customer Information with a third party without your knowledge and consent.
Does 24HourDigitizing.com use "IP Addresses" and cookies?
24HourDigitizing.com uses IP Addresses and Cookies in limited ways, as follows:
IP Addresses: An IP address is literally your computer's address and is a unique identifier, allowing online information to be sent to the right place. We use IP addresses to better understand the customer database. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information such as geographic distribution of our members. We do not intentionally link your IP address to your personally identifiable information.
24HourDigitizing.com Cookies: Contrary to popular belief, cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer's memory. The job of a cookie is to record only information you volunteer to us upon registering or visiting the site. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer the first time you visit our Web site that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are next time you come back. 24HourDigitizing.com cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information. Currently, 24HourDigitizing.com intends to make only limited use of cookies for the purpose of delivering content and ads specific to your interests. For instance cookies may be used to retain your personal preferences, hold session information for a "shopping cart" or save your password so it doesn't have to be re-entered each time you log in.
What are the safeguards and security procedures in place to protect your
information from loss, misuse, or alteration?
Your Customer Information on our Service is password-protected. We strongly recommend that you do not give your password to anyone and that you change it every 3 months. You may edit your 24HourDigitizing.com account information by using your 24HourDigitizing.com member name and password.
If you are using a public computer (public library, school computer, etc.) or a shared computer (family computer, roommate's computer, etc.), we strongly recommend that you sign out of your 24HourDigitizing.com account and close your browser before getting up and moving away from the computer.
24HourDigitizing.com employs SSL - a specialized encryption and security technology -- to protect your Customer Information. We understand that this is especially important when there is an exchange of credit card, billing and password information. In addition, we limit access of Customer Information to only those employees who need it to carry out their jobs.
24HourDigitizing.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email.
You will only be asked for your member name and password when you initiate the contact and only if the member name and password are necessary to correct a service problem.
How can you update or correct Customer Information?
Customer Information that you provide during registration is available in your 24HourDigitizing.com online account. To edit your Customer Information, you must enter your login and password to access your account. You may edit your account information at any time.
You can also cancel your 24HourDigitizing.com membership by contacting 24HourDigitizing.com. If you request cancellation of your account, 24HourDigitizing.com may (but is not required to) remove any and all content or other personal information from the 24HourDigitizing.com site, and your orders may not be accessible to you even if you choose to rejoin or reactivate your account at a later date. Information necessary for the purposes of maintaining business records regarding a cancelled account, including records of credit transactions and account ownership, will be retained in accordance with applicable law.
Notification of Change: If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner that is materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice, we will also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Contacting 24HourDigitizing.com:
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us
© 2020 24 Hour Digitizing. All Rights Reserved.
